envywomen.com 2016-02-09

# Privacy Policy – Envywomen.com

EnvyWomen is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This privacy policy tells you about the information we collect on this website and how we use that information. By using the EnvyWomen , you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy, which may be modified from time to time by us.

Children Under 13

We care about protecting the privacy of children. We won’t knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personally identifying information (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).

Information We Collect

The information we gather falls into two categories:

Information you supply when you register to receive emails or comment on the website, and  
Tracking information collected as you navigate through our site.

Personally Identifying Information

In operating the Site, EnvyWomen may include registration, comment forms, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, and other contact information.

Tracking Information

Cookies

From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Web site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our website other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Web site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

Click Tracking

As is true of most websites,EnvyWomen gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

IP Addresses

Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on EnvyWomen . This information is never provided to the third parties, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to personal information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Site.

Advertising

If there is advertising on EnvyWomen , such advertising may employ the use of cookies or other methods to track hits and click-throughs. We are not responsible for advertiser cookies or how the information gathered through their use might be used.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Participation on a Public Website

You should be aware that any personal information you submit on EnvyWomen in the comments may be read, collected, or used by other users of this Site, including anonymous visitors.

How Your Information Will Be Used

Personal Information

We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to EnvyWomen , or to send you additional information about EnvyWomen

Anonymous Information

We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

Use of Cookies

We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on EnvyWomen  
Protect and defend the rights or property of EnvyWomen or the users of this site, or  
Act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of this site.

Security

EnvyWomen has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

Comments  
EnvyWomen may include interactive forms such as comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Third Party Websites

EnvyWomen may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on EnvyWomen  and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
